>> Jem Young: 希望每个人都能创造出一条道路，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So hopefully everybody
was able to create a path,
不管你想要什么
call it whatever you want.
我选择了演示而不是标题
I chose demo, and instead of header and
表示我们使用 res.set。
express we use res.set.
我们表示 res.status ，而不是状态，因此设置您想要的任何状态。
And instead of status, we say res.status,
so set any status you want.
发送只是发送一些文本数据。
And send is just sending
down some text data.
你不必这么做但我觉得这很有趣
You don't have to do that, but
I thought it was pretty funny.
我们来看看这个
Let's check this out.
只要刷新页面就可以了
Just refresh the page, and there we go.
我要把 418 号当状态码
I'm getting 418 as a status code.
上面说我是个茶壶因为 [ LAUGH]
It says I'm a teapot because [LAUGH] yeah.
如果我们想看看头我们就进去
And if we wanna look at the headers,
we just go in there and
我们看到这个 X 是充满生命的
we see this X full stacked for life.
只是定制标题。
Just a custom header.
所以，定制标题是一种非常强大的直接发送方式
So again, custom headers are a really
powerful way of just sending down
此请求的一次性数据，因为数据是无状态的。
this one-time data for this request,
because data are stateless.
请求无状态。
Requests are stateless.
我们可以通过发送定制标题来设置临时状态。
We could set a temporary state
by sending a custom header.
例如，当您设置 200 以外的标题时，另一个时间为 401，
An example, another time when you set
a header other than 200 would be a 401,
未经授权。
not authorized.
因此，您可以检查 cookie，对有效 cookie 的数据库进行检查，或者
So you can check the cookie, check
against a database of valid cookies or
有效的登录凭证。
valid login credentials.
如果他们不是每一个请求都登录
And then if they're not logged in for
every single request,
你会写一些只返回 401的中间件
you'd write some middleware
that just returns a 401.
这意味着没有授权，这意味着你没有登录。
Which means not authorised,
which means hey, you're not logged in.
应用程序可以返回 401，这只是错误。
The app can either return 401,
which is just gonna error.
或者你可以处理它说，嘿，如果我收到 401 请求，你需要登录。
Or you can handle it and say, hey,
you need to log in if I get a 401 request.
在我们前进之前，任何关于标题，状态码的问题，都是这样的吗 ?
Any questions on headers, status codes,
things like that before we move on?
好了大家都开始工作了吗
All right, everybody get this working?
>> 演讲者 2: X 标题区分大小写吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is
the X-header case-sensitive?
>> Jem Young: 否，好的问题。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: No, good question.
你想要什么都可以
It can be anything you want.
通常，您可以发送您想要的任何标题，只要它是
Generally you can send down any
header that you want as long as it's
而不是那些众所周知的人
not one of the ones that are well-known.
所以就像 X-EPP-内容， X-EPP-语言，类似的东西。
So like X-EPP-Content,
X-EPP-Language, things like that.
X 只是一个标准，这是一个自定义的标题。
The X is just a standard for
saying, this is a custom header.
我不指望你做任何事
I don't expect you to do anything with it.
我知道该怎么做
I know what to do or
就像我在这个请求上附加的一些辅助元数据一样。
just like some ancillary metadata
that I'm attaching to this request.
希望每个人都能得到这个工作，如果不是，很酷。
Hopefully everybody's able to
get this working, if not, cool.
好吧好吧
All right.